Good days are really back.
There are nearly 4200 Religions in this world.
And thousands of people Die for it, kill for it every day
But people like you have created a new religion.
Corruption!
Whoever the killer is...
He's not some ordinary criminal.
In his mind, he's a soldier.
Who is fighting for the truth...
and wants it to triumph lies.
I will make your death such that...
you burn in this lifetime
...but feel the pain in your next life as well
I'm done catching small fish.
Time to catch a crocodile now.
No one has the right to take the Law into their own hands...
...except for the Law itself.
We, the protectors of the law, will reduce him to ashes.
YES SIR!
We won't spare him.
Are you a serial killer?
The one who's killing Police officers in the city?
Maybe?
Your eyes don't look like that of a killer
Our bullets till date are very impactful
You can't escape.
You don't need a 9mm bullet to take a life...
...all you need is a heart full of courage.
You took an oath to say true to your uniform, to your duty.
Now I've taken an oath, father.
To restore the honor of this medal.
Those who don't deserve to wear the uniform...
I will burn them to ashes.
Try and stop me
I will stop you and I will kill you..
Are you listening?
Hit him.
See how strong a woman can be.
Now not one man will ever taunt someone saying, "Are you a girl?"